BadCreditLoans.com Open nav Close nav [Skip to the content](#site-content)

Our service is free, but we may be compensated for [**sharing your info and marketing non-loan products**](https://www.badcreditloans.com/disclosure/) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.badcreditloans.com/privacy-policy/)

### Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated January 10, 2023

We recognize, respect and protect the personal privacy rights of all our users and work diligently to safeguard your privacy. We are committed to providing a high level of security and privacy regarding the collection and use of our users’ personal information, as well as the personal information of all consumers who visit our website. The following privacy policy explains how we use and protect the information about our users and all consumers who visit our website. We ask that you read it carefully. By using our website or our services, you hereby consent to this privacy policy (“Policy”) and agree to its terms.

Facts: What Do We Do with Your Personal Information?
----------------------------------------------------

### Why?

Companies choose how they share your personal information. Consumers have the right to limit some but not all sharing. We are committed to telling you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this policy carefully to understand what we do.

### What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on whether you simply browse our website or whether you submit a loan request on our website. This information generally includes, but is not limited to:

1. Information you enter on our website or a website in our network, such as:
    1. Personal information like your name and date of birth.
    2. Age, including whether you are 40 years old or older
    3. Social Security number, driver’s license number, and/or other similar identifiers
    4. Employment and income information
    5. Active military duty status
    6. Banking account information
    7. Contact information like your email address, phone number, and physical address (including how long you’ve been at that address)
    8. Loan information like the amount requested, the loan reason, and when you prefer to be contacted
    9. Your communications with us
2. Tracking data such as:
    1. internet protocol addresses,
    2. browser / application type,
    3. Internet Service Provider,
    4. date/time stamp,
    5. referring/exit pages, and
    6. your activity on our site
3. Geolocation data

### How?

Companies like ours need to share users’ personal information to run their everyday business. When we disclose personal information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to keep that personal information confidential. In the sections below, we list the reasons we use and share users’ personal information and whether you can limit this sharing.

Our Use of Your Personal Information
------------------------------------

We may use personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:

1. To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you provide us with personal information in order for us to connect you with a lender, we will use that information to try to connect you with a lender.
2. To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. For example, to provide you with information about loans in response to your loan request.
3. To provide you with email alerts and other notices concerning our products or services, or events or news, that may be of interest to you. For example, to provide you with information about other consumer financial products or services that may be of interest to you, such as credit monitoring, debt relief and credit cards.
4. To improve our website and present its contents to you, including creating an account using the information you provide on our website so you can easily submit loan inquiries in the future.
5. For testing, research, analysis and product development.
6. To improve our systems and algorithms.
7. To prevent, identify, investigate, and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical, or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.
8. As necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our clients or others.
9. To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
10. As described to you when collecting your personal information.
11. To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred.
12. To create an account for you so that you can more easily submit loan inquiries in the future on this website and our affiliated websites using your previously-provided information.
13. Other uses which you expressly consent to.

For more information on how we make money using your data, see our [Ad Disclosure](https://www.badcreditloans.com/disclosure/).

Sharing Your Personal Information
---------------------------------

### Reasons We May Share Your Personal Information

### Do We Share

### Can You Limit This Sharing

For our everyday business purposes – such as to try to connect you with a lender, process your transactions, or allow you to more easily submit loan requests in the future.

Yes

At the time you submit a loan request: No

Any time after you submit a loan request: Yes

For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you

Yes

At the time you submit a loan request: No

Any time after you submit a loan request: Yes

For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – to facilitate our everyday business purposes and our marketing purposes described above.

Yes

No

For non-affiliates to market to you – to market loans in response to your loan request.

Yes

At the time you submit a loan request: No

Any time after you submit a loan request: Yes

For non-affiliates to market to you – to market other consumer financial products or services, such as credit repair, deft relief, credit cards, and banking services.

Yes

Yes

As required by law – to respond to court orders and legal investigations as required by law.

Yes

No

### Sharing your sensitive personal information

As used in this section:

* “Sensitive Personal Information” means any of the following information about you: (1) Social Security number; (2) financial institution account number; (3) credit or debit card information; (4) taxpayer identification number; (5) passport number; (6) a driver’s license number or other government-issued identification number; (7) date of birth (other than year); (8) any other information by which your financial account can be accessed, or by which a you might be charged for goods or services, including through third parties such as telecommunications carriers.
* “Financial Product or Service” means any product, service, plan, or program represented, expressly or by implication, to (1) provide any consumer, arrange for any consumer to receive, or assist any consumer in receiving a loan or other extension of credit; (2) provide any consumer, arrange for any consumer to receive, or assist any consumer in receiving credit, debit, or stored value cards; (3) improve, repair, or arrange to improve or repair any consumer’s credit record, credit history, or credit rating; or (4) provide information about or provide assistance to improve any consumer’s credit record, credit history, or credit rating.

We will not share your Sensitive Personal Information unless you have requested a Financial Product or Service and (a) the sharing is necessary for a third party to provide the requested Financial Product or Service, (b) we have your express, informed consent for the sharing, and (c) we have conducted certain required screening of the recipients of your Sensitive Personal Information. However, we may share your Sensitive Personal Information where required under applicable law. (For example, to respond to court orders and legal investigations as required by law.)

### Categories of Non-Affiliates We Share Your Information With

1. Lenders
2. Networks of lenders
3. Agents of record for lenders
4. Financial technology companies that offer loans in partnership with licensed banks.
5. Other non-affiliates that may be able to offer you or market consumer financial products or services related to your loan request (for example, debit repair and credit monitoring services)
6. Other non-affiliate service providers to facilitate our marketing to you.

For more information on how we make money using your data, see our [Ad Disclosure](https://www.badcreditloans.com/disclosure/).

### To limit our sharing

Call this toll-free number: (800) 245-5626

Email us at  

After your loan request has been completed, we may continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing of your information.

### Information we do not collect or share

We do not collect or share any of the following information about you: signature, physical characteristics or description, passport number, medical information, health insurance

### Here’s our Contact Info.

We take your privacy seriously and maintain a process to respond to your concerns regarding violations of this Policy. If you believe that we haven’t complied with this Policy in regard to your personal information or have questions regarding your privacy with us, please contact us using the information provided below. If you are reporting non-compliance with this Policy, please describe the issue in as much detail as possible without disclosing any sensitive information about you or third parties.

For questions please contact us at:

BadCreditLoans.com

(800) 245-5626

What We Do
----------

### How do we protect your personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with applicable law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

### How do we collect your personal information?

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

* Create an account
* Request a loan
* Provide information on our forms
* Navigate to or use our website
* Communicate with us
* Request a loan through a different website in our network

### Why can’t you limit all sharing at the time you submit a loan request?

You cannot limit all sharing at the time you submit a loan request because to connect you with a lender we need to share your information with our network of lenders and other networks of lenders so the lenders in these networks can choose whether to offer you a loan or market their loans to you. However, you can contact us at any time after you submit your loan request to limit all sharing.

Definitions
-----------

### Affiliates

Companies related by common ownership or control

* Our affiliates include companies under common ownership and control that provide us with technical and advertising services.

### Non-affiliates

Companies not related by common ownership and control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

* Non-affiliates we share with include service providers, cobranded partners, financial service companies, data processors, and advertisers.

Retention of your personal information
--------------------------------------

We use the following factors to determine the retention period of personal information:

* to allow you to more easily submit loan requests in the future and to otherwise facilitate future loan requests;
* to perform under applicable terms and services to which you agreed;
* as necessary in connection with the lawful purposes set out in this Policy;
* to comply with applicable laws; and
* to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

Other Important Information
---------------------------

### For California Residents

We will not share your information with non-affiliates except for our everyday business purposes, for marketing our products and services to you, or with your consent. Also see the section below titled “For California Residents Only.”

### For Vermont Residents

We will not share your information with nonaffiliates except as permitted by law or as authorized by you. We will not disclose credit information about you to our affiliates except with your consent or as required or permitted by law.

### For Nevada Residents

We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law. You may be placed on our Do Not Call List by calling (800) 772-2274. Or contact the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number: 1-702-486-3132; bcpinfo@ag.state,nv.us.

### Cookies

A cookie is a file which contains data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive. This data includes information about the visitor. A visitor has the option to reject a cookie and they still will be able to access our Website, however, the user may not have access to certain sections of our Website if cookies are disabled. The purpose of using cookies is to allow us to track the intent of our visitors and enhance visitor experience while using our Website. All cookies, including session cookies and persistent cookies, served on the Website are tied to PII that you provide. Our affiliates and partners may use cookies on our Website, however, we cannot control or access cookies set by third parties.

### Additional Sharing

We cannot guarantee that all of your information will not be disclosed in ways not covered in this Privacy Policy. There may be circumstances in which the disclosure of your information happens as result of unlawful interception or transmission to a third party. Also, a legal situation may occur in which the disclosure of your information or other information is required. Additionally, as we develop and grow, we may choose to buy additional businesses or assets, including user information. In the event that we or one or more of our assets are acquiring, user information may be one of the assets sold.

### Minors

We do not knowingly collect or disclose information from children under the age of 18. No information is knowingly collected from children or used for any purpose whatsoever, including marketing and promotional purposes. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 18 has provided us with PII through any point of contact, please contact us using the contact information provided above.

### Unsubscribe

You can remove your information from our contact list at any time with no questions asked. To remove your information from our database to no longer receive future communications from us, please contact us using the contact information provided below.

### Updates

We may update this Privacy Policy with any changes to our information practices. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to our information practices, we will revise this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you read and review this Privacy Policy each and every time you access our website and/or use any service referred to you by us. Your use of the website constitutes your agreement to the terms of the effective Privacy Policy.

For California Residents Only
-----------------------------

### Access to Specific Information

You can request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months, including:

1. The categories and sources of personal information we collected about you.
2. Our purpose for collecting or sharing that information.
3. The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information, including the categories of information each category of third parties received and the business reasons for sharing.
4. The specific pieces of personal information we collected (data portability request).

### Deletion Request Rights

We will delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.

We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) to:

* Complete the processing of your loan request or otherwise perform our contract with you.
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
* Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
* Exercise another provided for by law.
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.).

### Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights

To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by sending an email to support@badcreditloans.com with the exact subject line “California Resident Exercising Access, Data Portability, or Deletion Rights” or by calling (800) 245-5626.

Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information.

You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period.

The verifiable consumer request must: (a) Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative and (b) Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

### Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights

You have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information at any time by sending an email to [support@badcreditloans.com](mailto:support@badcreditloans.com) with the exact subject line “California Resident Personal Information Sales Opt-Out” or by calling (800) 245-5626.

### Non-Discrimination

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights described in this “For California Residents Only” section or any other rights granted to you under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018.

### Do Not Track (DNT) signals

We do not track our users over time and across third party websites, and therefore do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, we may use third-party services (e.g., Google Analytics) or have third-party advertising partners (e.g., Google, noted above) who may keep track of your browsing activities. You should review the specific privacy policies of these third parties at the following addresses to learn how they respond to DNT signals:

Google: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)  
Amazon: [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)  
Microsoft: [https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement/default.aspx](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement/default.aspx)

### California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83)

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of this site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [support@badcreditloans.com](mailto:support@badcreditloans.com) with the exact subject line “California Resident Shine the Light Request”.

### Other Disclosures

All of the categories of information described in the “What Do We Do with Your Personal Information?” section above have been collected and disclosed by us in the preceding 12 months.

### Request up to $10,000

* Loans

* Scam Alert – Stay Informed

* Legal

* Learn More

* OLA Consumer Hotline
    
    As a proud member of the Online Lenders Alliance (OLA), BadCreditLoans.com is serious about protecting your personal information. The OLA consumer hotline is a key consumer resource, for questions on lending or reporting possible occurrences of fraud.

Copyright © 2024 Bad Credit Loans. All Rights Reserved.

BadCreditLoans.com ("BadCreditLoans.com" or "we" or "our") owns and operates the website located at BadCreditLoans.com (the "Site"). BadCreditLoans.com provides and maintains this site for your information, conditioned on your acceptance, without modification, of the terms, conditions and notices contained in this Terms of Use.

**Legal Disclaimer:** The purpose of this website is to connect potential borrowers with the lenders and financial service providers that advertise on this website. The operator of this website is neither a lender nor a broker and does not make any credit decisions. This website merely takes information from consumers and forwards it to lenders and third parties who may be able to provide the types of loans that may meet the consumers needs. For those consumers who do not qualify for a Personal Loan, we will refer you to alternative lenders and providers. This website shall not be considered an offer or solicitation for a loan. There is no guarantee that you will be approved for any type of loan. We do not charge you for the service we provide and are not a representative or agent of any lender or third party provider. We are compensated by lenders and third parties. The time it takes for money to transfer to your account will vary by lender and also depend on your individual financial institution. You may be required to fax information to your lender in order to receive a loan. This service and lenders are not available in all states. If you have any question regarding the details of your loan, you should contact your lender directly. Personal loans and other types of loans should not be considered a long term financial solution. They are means to provide short term financing to solve immediate financial needs. Lenders and third party providers may perform a credit check with one or more credit agencies. These credit checks can have an impact on your credit score. By submitting your request, you are authorizing the lenders and third party providers to independently verify the information you submitted and your credit worthiness. Non-payment of credit could result in collection activities and your lender may report late payment history to consumer reporting agencies which could impact future lending decisions by your current lender or other future lenders. Nothing on this website shall constitute an offer or solicitation for a loan.

**Availability:** Residents of some states in the U.S. may not qualify for a bad credit loan as a result of certain lender requirements. The Website does not guarantee that completing a loan request form will result in you being offered a loan product by a lender, or you being offered a product with rates or terms as desired.

Contact Us.

Badcreditloans.com is powered by Great LLC

Address: 2661 N Pearl St #431

Tacoma, WA 98407

Telephone Number: 800-245-5626

Email address: support@badcreditloans.com
